A Guide to the American Lung Association of Virginia (ALAV) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- VTRDA Board Meeting 1968, 7-photos, 8-negatives (Box-folder 259:022)
- VTRDA Trainees 1968, 49-photos, 22-negatives (Box-folder 259:023)
- MCV-UVA Conference September, 1969, 3-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 260:001)
- Miscellaneous Photos 1969, 4-photos, 10-negatives (Box-folder 260:002)
- Miss Christmas Seal Contest 1969, 20-photos (Box-folder 260:003)
- NTRDA Annual Meeting 1969, 1-photo (Box-folder 260:004)
- Shenandoah Nursing Seminar October, 1969, 19-photos (Box-folder 260:005)
- Southeastern TB Association Tangier Project 1969, 2-photos (Box-folder 260:006)
- TB Exhibit Posters 1969, 3-photos (Box-folder 260:007)
- TB Sunday at Harrisonburg April 5, 1969, 7-photos (Box-folder 260:008)
- Tuberculin Testing February, 1969, 20-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 260:009)
- Unknown Photos September, 1969, 3-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 260:010)
- VTRDA Annual Meeting 1969, 11-photos, 11-negatives (Box-folder 260:011)
- VTRDA Board Meeting October, 1969, 23-photos, 23-negatives (Box-folder 260:012)
- VTRDA Trainees 1969, 20-photos, 4-negatives (Box-folder 260:013)
- Youth Ambassadors 1969, 8-photos (Box-folder 260:014)
- Youth Board 1969, 16-negatives (Box-folder 260:015)
- Blue Ridge Sanatorium Patients February, 1970, 39-photos, 29-negatives (Box-folder 261:001)
- Dr. Stringer Emergency Care 1970, 2-photos, 53-negatives (Box-folder 261:002)
- First State Youth Board Meeting 1970, 1-photo (Box-folder 261:003)
- John B. Cary School Children 1970, 2-photos, 2-negatives (Box-folder 261:004)
- Governor Linwood Holton and Miss Christmas Seal 1970, 7-photos (Box-folder 261:005)
- Intensive Care Van and Paramedical Emergency Technicians Exhibits 1970, 10-photos, 8-negatives (Box-folder 261:006)
- Joint Board Meeting and Board Dinner October 9,1970, 10-photos, 28-negatives (Box-folder 261:007)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1970 1970, 5-photos (Box-folder 261:008)
- Nora Spencer Hamner Award to Ray Seward 1970, 1-photo, 2-negatives (Box-folder 261:009)
- Performance of "Leave it to Laurie" at Program Planning Conference 1970, 1-photo (Box-folder 261:010)
- Portsmouth Southern Junior Board 1970, 1-photo (Box-folder 261:011)
- Smoking Posters 1970, 2-photos (Box-folder 261:012)
- Southern TB-RD Christmas Seal Campaign 1970, 19-photos (Box-folder 261:013)
- Southside Health Careers Seminar 1970, 2-photos (Box-folder 261:014)
- Southside Youth Board 1970, 2-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 261:015)
- Suffolk Emphysema Clinic March, 1970, 9-photos, 6-negatives (Box-folder 261:016)
- Suffolk High School Club Representatives November, 1970, 3-photos (Box-folder 261:017)
- Suffolk Women's Club 1970, 1-photo (Box-folder 261:018)
- Tangier Island TB Project 1970, 58-photos, 7-negatives (Box-folder 261:019)
- TB Conference November 16-17, 1970, 10-photos (Box-folder 261:020)
- Virginia Youth Ambassadors 1970, 2-photos (Box-folder 261:021)
- VTRDA Annual Meeting May, 1970, 18-photos, 21-negatives (Box-folder 261:022)
- Youth Board Representatives to NTRDA Annual Meeting May, 1970, 27-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 261:023)
- Youth Ecology Seminar November 21, 1970, 14-photos (Box-folder 261:024)
- Blue Ridge Sanatorium June 29, 1971, 14-negatives (Box-folder 262:001)
- Virginia Council on State Legislation December 2-3, 1971, 18-negatives (Box-folder 262:002)
- Bronco Junction: Richmond Workshop for Teachers on Berkeley Project 1972, 18-photos (Box-folder 262:003)
- Buckingham Community Health Center Patient 1972, 2-photos (Box-folder 262:004)
- Carpool Day May 2, 1972, 9-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 262:005)
- Central Virginia Community Health Center January 18, 1972, 12-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 262:006)
- Roanoke Nursing Seminar on Respiratory Disease 1972, 2-photos (Box-folder 262:007)
- VLA Annual Meeting April 19-20, 1972, 37-negatives (Box-folder 262:008)
- VLA Executive Committee Members at Eastern Virginia Medical School August 7, 1972, 2-photos, 9-negatives (Box-folder 262:009)
- Youth Board Annual Meeting May 13, 1972, 10-photos (Box-folder 262:010)
- Clean Hair Week October 14-21, 1973, 1-photo (Box-folder 262:011)
- Dr. O'Donohue Award May, 1973, 2-negatives (Box-folder 262:012)
- Earl Hamner and Youth Board 1973, 13-photos (Box-folder 262:013)
- Interagency Council March 12, 1973, 1-negative (Box-folder 262:014)
- John Boy and Youth Board 1973, 14-photos (Box-folder 262:015)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1973 1973, 11-photos, 19-negatives (Box-folder 262:016)
- Northern Virginia Annual Meeting April 25, 1973, 5-negatives (Box-folder 262:017)
- Panel - The Killers 1973, 1-photo (Box-folder 262:018)
- Photos Used in "How Can I Help?" 1973, 15-photos (Box-folder 262:019)
- Public Relations Committee Meeting May, 1973, 2-negatives (Box-folder 262:020)
- Southside Annual Meeting May, 1973, 3-negatives (Box-folder 262:021)
- Southside Youth Board - Youth Interchange 1973, 2-negatives (Box-folder 262:022)
- VLA Annual Meeting April 12, 1973, 15-negatives (Box-folder 262:023)
- Youth Interchange March 10, 1973, 21-photos, 32-negatives (Box-folder 262:024)
- Battle to Breathe 1974, 1-slides (Box-folder 263:001)
- Berkeley Project at Fox School 1974, 2-photos (Box-folder 263:002)
- Demonstration Therapy for Life and Breath Patients 1974-1975, 4-negatives (Box-folder 263:003)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1974 1974, 13-photos, 10-negatives, 9-slides (Box-folder 263:004)
- Mrs. Goodwin and Christmas Seal of 1974 1974, 12-photos (Box-folder 263:005)
- Richmond Nursing Seminar 1974, 16-photos, 10-negatives (Box-folder 263:006)
- Richmond Walkathon 1974, 1-photo (Box-folder 263:007)
- Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center 1974, 2-photos (Box-folder 263:008)
- Youth Board 1974, 25-photos, 21-negatives (Box-folder 263:009)
- Youth Board Walk-A-Thon 1974, 3-photos, 11-negatives (Box-folder 263:010)
- Annual Meeting - Awards Winners 1975, 10-negatives (Box-folder 263:011)
- Berkeley Project 1975, 40-photos, 4-negatives (Box-folder 263:012)
- Bike-A-Thon 1975, 3-photos, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 263:013)
- Bronco Junction 1975, 1-photo (Box-folder 263:014)
- Central Virginia Youth Board Picnic 1975, 16-photos (Box-folder 263:015)
- Christmas Seal Painting 1975, 2-photos (Box-folder 263:016)
- Conference on Pulmonary Disease 1975, 1-photo (Box-folder 263:017)
- Donation of Soroptimist Club for Medical Education November 12, 1975, 3-photos (Box-folder 263:018)
- Happy Breath Day 1975, 27-photos (Box-folder 263:019)
- Miscellaneous Slides of 1975 1975, 3-slides (Box-folder 263:020)
- Nora Spencer Hamner Award to Mrs. Murden 1975, 4-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 263:021)
- VLA Walkathon 1975, 2-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 263:022)
- Youth Board 1975, 35-photos, 14-negatives (Box-folder 263:023)
- Bowl-A-Thon December 24, 1976, 13-photos, 15-negatives (Box-folder 264:001)
- Child Chest Clinic 1976, 4-photos, 2-negatives (Box-folder 264:002)
- Christmas Seal of 1976 1976, 1-photo, 5-negatives (Box-folder 264:003)
- Cleaner Air Week October 9, 1976, 1-photo (Box-folder 264:004)
- Lisa Garner and VLA Walkathon 1976, 2-photos, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 264:005)
- Miss Christmas Seal Contest 1976, 1-photo (Box-folder 264:006)
- Nursing Seminar on Respiratory Diseases 1976, 1-photo, 2-slides (Box-folder 264:007)
- Southwest Mines and Lonesome Pine Hospital 1976, 9-photo, 10-negatives (Box-folder 264:008)
- VLA Annual Meeting 1976, 1-photo (Box-folder 264:009)
- VLA Walkathon October 17, 1976, 25-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 264:010)
- Unknown Slides of 1976 1976, 2-slides (Box-folder 264:011)
- Youth Board 1976, 3-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 264:012)
- Family Asthma Program 1977, 18-photos, 23-negatives (Box-folder 264:013)
- Richmond Walkathon October, 1977, 1-photo, 4-negatives (Box-folder 264:014)
- VLA Annual Meeting 1977, 13-photos, 14-negatives (Box-folder 264:015)
- Superkids at the University of Richmond 1977, 2-photos (Box-folder 264:016)
- VLA Program Workshop 1977, 11-slides (Box-folder 264:017)
- Balloon Day 1978, 2-photos (Box-folder 265:001)
- Better Breathing Program 1978, 4-photos, 4-negatives (Box-folder 265:002)
- Berkeley Project 1978, 17-photos, 20-negatives, 10-slides (Box-folder 265:003)
- Cathy Baker and Christmas Seal of 1978 1978, 14-photos (Box-folder 265:004)
- Emphysema Clinic 1978, 2-photos (Box-folder 265:005)
- Happy Breath Day 1978, 8-photos, 10-negatives (Box-folder 265:006)
- Life and Breath Patient Picnic June, 1978, 11-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 265:007)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1978 1978, 19-photos, 11-negatives, 24-slides (Box-folder 265:008)
- Richmond Walkathon October, 1978, 7-negatives (Box-folder 265:009)
- Roanoke Life and Breath Clinic 1978, 15-photos (Box-folder 265:010)
- VLA Annual Meeting March 30, 1978, 5-photos, 15-negatives (Box-folder 265:011)
- VLA Youth Board Fair Exhibit September 6, 1978, 1-photo (Box-folder 265:012)
- Youth Board 1978, 32-photos, 15-negatives (Box-folder 265:013)
- Kite Day 1979, 3-photos, 6-negatives (Box-folder 266:001)
- Life and Breath Picnic 1979, 4-slides (Box-folder 266:002)
- Miscellaneous Slides of 1979 1979, 5-slides (Box-folder 266:003)
- Proclamation of Carpool Day May 2, 1979, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:004)
- Superkids Day 1979, 3-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 266:005)
- VLA Fall Board Meeting 1979, 10-photos,18-negatives (Box-folder 266:006)
- Volunteers for Christmas Mail 1979, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:007)
- Youth Board 1979, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:008)
- Emporia Jr. Women's Club October 25, 1980, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:009)
- Family Asthma at Chimborazo School 1980, 2-photos,1-negative, 61-slides (Box-folder 266:010)
- Nursing Seminar November, 1980, 2-photos,9-negatives (Box-folder 266:011)
- Planning Committee for Symposium 1980, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:012)
- Roanoke Life and Breath Clinic 1980-1981, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:013)
- Summer Scholarship 1980, 3-photos (Box-folder 266:014)
- Vietnamese Refugees in Arlington August, 1980, 5-photos,4-negatives (Box-folder 266:015)
- VLA Annual Meeting 1980, 8-photos,10-negatives (Box-folder 266:016)
- ALAV Fall Board Meeting and Nora Spencer Hamner Award 1981, 2-photos,3-negatives (Box-folder 266:017)
- Bike-A-Lung 1981, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:018)
- Christmas Seal of 1981 1981, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:019)
- Hike-Emporia 1981, 7-negatives (Box-folder 266:020)
- Hike-A-Thon 1981, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:021)
- Lung Exhibits 1981, 32-photos,9-negatives (Box-folder 266:022)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1981 1981, 11-photos,23-negatives (Box-folder 266:023)
- Town Meeting on Clean Air 1981, 6-photos,6-negatives (Box-folder 266:024)
- Virginia Craft Guild December 1, 1981, 1-photo (Box-folder 266:025)
- VLA Annual Meeting 1981, 1-negatives (Box-folder 266:026)
- ALAV Shenandoah Region February 24, 1982, 4-photos (Box-folder 267:001)
- Blue Ridge Bike-a-thon October 3, 1982, 13-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 267:002)
- Christmas Seal Reception 1982, 3-negatives (Box-folder 267:003)
- Clean Air Town Meeting 1982, 2-photos (Box-folder 267:004)
- Freedom From Smoking Clinic March, 1982, 5-photos, 7-negatives (Box-folder 267:005)
- Hike-A-Thon April, 1982, 1-photo (Box-folder 267:006)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1982 1982, 9-photos, 7-negatives, 3-slides (Box-folder 267:007)
- Northern Region Name Change Party February 23, 1982, 3-photos, 4-negatives, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 267:008)
- Richmond Region Board Meeting 1982, 6-negatives (Box-folder 267:009)
- Richmond Region Christmas Seal Reception 1982, 6-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 267:010)
- Richmond Region Christmas Tree December, 1982, 1-photo (Box-folder 267:011)
- Smoking Education - Teacher's Workshop 1982, 4-negatives (Box-folder 267:012)
- Swift Creek Elementary School March, 1982, 3-photos, 4-negatives (Box-folder 267:013)
- Twins: Smoking and Pregnancy 1982, 5-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 267:014)
- Air Pollution Monitoring May 10, 1983, 2-photos (Box-folder 267:015)
- ALANV Open House at Fairfax November, 1983, 1-photo (Box-folder 267:016)
- ALAV Annual Meeting June 25, 1983, 6-negative (Box-folder 267:017)
- ALAV Building 1983, 5-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 267:018)
- ALAV Christmas Seal Campaign 1983, 2-photos (Box-folder 267:019)
- Andree Brooke 1983, 2-negatives (Box-folder 267:020)
- Bike-A-Thon 1983, 5-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 267:021)
- Christmas Seal of 1983 1983, 16-photos, 9-negatives, 4-newspaper clippings (Box-folder 267:022)
- Christmas Seal Volunteers November, 1983, 7-photos (Box-folder 267:023)
- Clean Air Week May 2-8, 1983, 14-photos, 6-negatives (Box-folder 267:024)
- Fairfield Elementary School Novmeber, 1983, 2-photos (Box-folder 267:025)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1983 1983, 8-photos, 4-negatives, 5-newspaper clippings, 4-slides (Box-folder 267:026)
- Nora Spencer Hamner Award 1983, 1-photo (Box-folder 267:027)
- Richmond Region Lung Club Meeting September, 1983, 1-photo (Box-folder 267:028)
- Richmond Region Yard Sale October 15, 1983, 7-photos, 2-negatives (Box-folder 267:029)
- Staff Christmas Luncheon December, 1983, 1-photo (Box-folder 267:030)
- Tidewater Region Tree of Donations December, 1983, 2-photos (Box-folder 267:031)
- Volunteers Reception December 25, 1983, 12-photos, 2-negatives (Box-folder 267:032)
- ALAV 75th Anniversary 1984, 53-photos, 15-negatives (Box-folder 268:001)
- ALAV Board Meeting January, 1984, 22-photos, 10-negatives (Box-folder 268:002)
- ALAV Richmond Region Picnic 1984, 5-negatives (Box-folder 268:003)
- Berkeley Project 1984, 20-photos, 7-negatives (Box-folder 268:004)
- Cathy Baker and 1260 WCHV Charlottesville Radio Station November, 1984, 26-photos, 7-negatives (Box-folder 268:005)
- Christmas Seal Tree Promotion in Roanoke December, 1984, 3-photos (Box-folder 268:006)
- Mayor Leafe of Norfolk in Christmas Parade 1984, 2-photos (Box-folder 268:007)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1984 1984, 3-photos (Box-folder 268:008)
- Miss Christmas Seal Contest in Suffolk January 4, 1984, 13-photos, 5-negatives, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 268:009)
- Needlepoint Design of No Smoking Sign 1984, 1-photos, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 268:010)
- Southeast Region ALAV Asthma Seminar November 11-12, 1984, 5-photos (Box-folder 268:011)
- Volunteer Party 1984, 12-photos (Box-folder 268:012)
- Air Pollution Primer Presentation May 23, 1985, 1-photo (Box-folder 269:001)
- ALAV Annual Meeting June 13, 1985, 20-photos, 2-negatives (Box-folder 269:002)
- ALAV Annual Report 1985, 7-photos (Box-folder 269:003)
- ALAV Winter Board Meeting 1985, 7-photos, 8-negatives (Box-folder 269:004)
- Benefit Baseball Game at John S. Battle High School March 16, 1985, 9-photos (Box-folder 269:005)
- Bessie Weller Elementary School May 24, 1985, 7-photos (Box-folder 269:006)
- Festival of Life March, 1985, 5-photos (Box-folder 269:007)
- Health Fair at Albemarle High School April 24, 1985, 5-photos (Box-folder 269:008)
- Highlands Workshop August, 1985, 2-photos (Box-folder 269:009)
- Miscellaneous Photos 1985, 33-photos (Box-folder 269:010)
- New Airways 1985, 8-photos (Box-folder 269:011)
- Photo Shoot in a Restaurant 1985, 70-photos, 15-negatives, 2-slides (Box-folder 269:012)
- Program Planning Conference March, 1985, 22-photos, 6-negatives (Box-folder 270:001)
- Richmond Region Christmas Seal Reception 1985, 4-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 270:002)
- Shenandoah Region Elementary School Poster Contest 1985, 16-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 270:003)
- Southside Region National Respiratory Week October 6-12, 1985, 1-photo (Box-folder 270:004)
- Staff of Roberts Oxygen April, 1985, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 270:005)
- Stage Show Rehearsal 1985, 64-photos, 15-negatives (Box-folder 270:006)
- Virginia Highlands July 9, 1985, 6-photos (Box-folder 270:007)
- Airways 1986, 22-photos, 11-negatives (Box-folder 271:001)
- ALAV Exhibits November, 1986, 4-photos (Box-folder 271:002)
- Annual Report 1986, 17-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 271:003)
- Beta Club GCHS December 19, 1986, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 271:004)
- Miscellaneous Photos of 1986 1986, 11-photoss (Box-folder 271:005)
- WXEX-TV Anchors, 1986 December 5-14, 1986, 2-newspaper clippings (Box-folder 271:006)
- No Smoking Sign in the Poff Federal Building February 6, 1987, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 271:007)
- West Virginia Ski Privilege Card January 14, 1987, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 271:008)
- Asthma Shots for Clean Air Week N.D., 1-photo, 4-negatives (Box-folder 272:001)
- Berkeley Project N.D., 4-photos (Box-folder 272:002)
- Big Stone Gap Program Advisory Council with J. Coffman N.D., 1-photo (Box-folder 272:003)
- Bike-A-Thon N.D., 5-photos (Box-folder 272:004)
- Black Lung Symposium N.D., 6-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 272:005)
- Buildings N.D., 5-photos, 3-negatives (Box-folder 272:006)
- Carpool Day N.D., 8-photos (Box-folder 272:007)
- Central Virginia Health Education Center N.D., 3-negatives (Box-folder 272:008)
- Children N.D., 46-photos (Box-folder 272:009)
- Christmas Seal Volunteers Party N.D., 8-photos (Box-folder 272:010)
- Cigarette Advertisement N.D., 13-photos, 8-negatives (Box-folder 272:011)
- Clean Air Award N.D., 3-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 272:012)
- Doctors N.D., 22-photos, 6-negatives (Box-folder 272:013)
- Emergency Care N.D., 9-photos (Box-folder 272:014)
- Hamner, Earl N.D., 5-negatives (Box-folder 272:015)
- Health Careers Fair N.D., 3-negatives (Box-folder 272:016)
- Health Career- Phantasmagoria N.D., 2-photos, 7-negatives (Box-folder 272:017)
- Hike-A-Thon N.D., 1-photo (Box-folder 272:018)
- John B. Cary Class N.D., 5-negatives (Box-folder 272:019)
- Lynchburg Clean Air Press Conference N.D., 2-photos (Box-folder 272:020)
- No Smoking Posters N.D., 6-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 273:001)
- Nurses N.D., 5-photos, 11-negatives (Box-folder 273:002)
- Octopuff and Happy Breath Day Cake N.D., 1-photo, 1-negative (Box-folder 273:003)
- Patients at Richmond Clinic N.D., 5-negatives (Box-folder 273:004)
- Peanut Bowl Parade N.D., 1-photo (Box-folder 273:005)
- Picnic N.D., 41-photos, 6-negatives (Box-folder 273:006)
- Pool Game N.D., 22-photos, 6-negatives, 1-newspaper clipping (Box-folder 273:007)
- Smokers N.D., 28-photos, 16-negatives, 1-slide (Box-folder 273:008)
- Southwest Craft Guild N.D., 1-photo (Box-folder 273:009)
- Therapists N.D., 24-photos (Box-folder 273:010)
- Tuberculin Testing N.D., 5-photos (Box-folder 273:011)
- Virginia Craft Guild N.D., 3-photos (Box-folder 273:012)
- Walk-A-Thon N.D., 1-photo (Box-folder 273:013)
- X-Ray Survey Unit N.D., 1-photo (Box-folder 273:014)
- Yard Sale N.D., 2-negatives (Box-folder 273:015)
- Youth Board N.D., 7-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 273:016)
- Youth Board Christmas Party at Blue Ridge Sanatorium N.D., 13-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 273:017)
- Youth Board Speakers Contest at Fisher School N.D., 4-negatives (Box-folder 273:018)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 41-photos, 4-negatives (Box-folder 274:001)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 27-photos, 1-negative (Box-folder 274:002)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 46-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 274:003)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 29-photos, 12-negatives (Box-folder 274:004)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 52-photos (Box-folder 274:005)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 56-photos (Box-folder 275:001)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 53-photos (Box-folder 275:002)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 27-photos, 5-negatives (Box-folder 275:003)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 112-negatives (Box-folder 275:004)
- Photos of Unknown People N.D., 121-negatives, 11-slides (Box-folder 275:005)
- VTA Minutes Book I March 22, 1910-October 1, 1926, 1-TD (Box-folder 276:001)
  Minute Book
- VTA Minutes Book II February 18, 1927-June 25, 1934, 1-TD (Box-folder 277:001)
- Virginia Thoracic Society Meeting Minutes December 12, 1953-March 17, 1969, 1-TD (Box-folder 277:002)
- VTRDA Meeting Minutes I June 4, 1964-December 31, 1969, 1-TD (Box-folder 278:001)
- VTRDA Meeting Minutes II March 5, 1970-December 31, 1976, 1-TD (Box-folder 278:002)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association I 1946-1950, 1-TD (Box-folder 279:001)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association II 1950-1954, 1-TD (Box-folder 279:002)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association III 1954-1957, 1-TD (Box-folder 280:001)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association IV 1958-1959, 1-TD (Box-folder 280:002)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association V 1959-1961, 1-TD (Box-folder 281:001)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association VI 1961-1962, 1-TD (Box-folder 281:002)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association VII 1963-1964, 1-TD (Box-folder 281:003)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association VIII 1965, 1-TD (Box-folder 282:001)
- Minutes of Richmond Tuberculosis Association IX 1966-1967, 1-TD (Box-folder 282:002)
- Minutes of the Junior Board of Directors Meetings 1966-1967, 1-TD (Box-folder 283:001)
- Minutes of the Herico County Tuberculosis Association April 15, 1944-May 4, 1961, 1-TD (Box-folder 283:002)
- Minutes of the Shenandoah County Tuberculosis Association I June 11, 1948-January 10, 1955, 1-TD (Box-folder 284:001)
- Minutes of the Shenandoah County Tuberculosis Association II May 9, 5/9-March 29, 1963, 1-TD (Box-folder 284:002)
- Minutes of the Fauquier County Tuberculosis Association I April 25, 1934-January 22, 1947, 1-TD (Box-folder 285:001)
- Minutes of the Fauquier County Tuberculosis Association II May 6, 1947-October 20, 1954, 1-TD (Box-folder 285:002)
- Minutes of the Fauquier County Tuberculosis Association III January 17, 1955-June 15, 1958, 1-TD (Box-folder 286:001)
- Minutes of the Fauquier County Tuberculosis Association IV Januayry 26, 1959-April 16, 1963, 1-TD (Box-folder 286:002)
- Minutes of the Front Royal Warren Tuberculosis Association I February 23, 1948-March 28, 1958, 1-TD (Box-folder 287:001)
- Minutes of the Front Royal Warren Tuberculosis Association II May 8, 1958-April 4, 1960, 1-TD (Box-folder 287:002)
- Minutes of the Goochland County Tuberculosis Association July 10, 1940-March 12, 1963, 1-AD (Box-folder 288:001)
- Minutes of the Goochland County Tuberculosis Association July 10, 1940-March 12, 1963, 1-AD (Box-folder 288:001)
- Minutes of the Chesterfield County Tuberculosis Association September 17, 1940-April 30, 1963, 1-TD (Box-folder 288:002)
- Minutes of the Warren-Rappahannock-Clark TB Association May 14, 1958-April 16, 1963, 1-TD (Box-folder 288:003)
- Minutes of the VTA Executive Committee Meeting (I) June 5, 1914-August 31, 1933, 1-TD (Box-folder 289:001)
- Minutes of the VTA Executive Committee Meeting (II) January 28, 1935-July 27, 1943, 1-TD (Box-folder 289:002)
- Minutes of the VTA Executive Committee Meeting (III) January 18, 1944-August 16, 1950, 1-TD (Box-folder 289:003)
- Minutes of the VTA Executive Committee Meeting (IV) September 7, 1950-March 16, 1955, 1-TD (Box-folder 290:001)
- Minutes of the VTA Executive Committee Meeting (V) March 17, 1955-June 10, 1960, 1-TD (Box-folder 290:002)
- Minutes of the VTA Executive Committee Meeting (VI) October 27, 1960-March 24, 1964, 1-TD (Box-folder 291:001)
- Richmond TB Association: Cash Receipts and Disbursements 1916 - 1919, 1-AD (Box-folder 292:001)
  Financial Book
- Richmond TB Association: Report on Audit of Cash Receipts and Disbursements 1920, 1-TD (Box-folder 292:002)
  Audit Report
- Richmond TB Association: Report on Audit of Cash Receipts and Disbursements 1921, 1-TD (Box-folder 292:003)
- Richmond TB Association: Report on Audit of Cash Receipts and Disbursements 1922, 1-TD (Box-folder 292:004)
- Richmond TB Association: Report on Audit of Cash Receipts and Disbursements 1923, 1-TD (Box-folder 292:005)
- Richmond TB Association: Report on Audit of Cash Receipts and Disbursements 1924, 1-TD (Box-folder 292:006)
- Richmond TB Association: Report on Audit of Cash Receipts and Disbursements 1925, 1-TD (Box-folder 292:007)